{
  "questions":[
  {
    "id": "1",
    "Question": "Who was the father of computer?",
    "Ans1": "Charlie Babbage",
    "Ans2": "Dennis Ritchie",
    "Ans3": "Charles Babbage",
    "Ans4": "Ken Thompson",
    "correct": "Charles Babbage"
  },
  {
    "id": "2",
    "Question": "What is the full form of ALU?",
    "Ans1": "Arithmetic Logic Unit",
    "Ans2": "Arithmetic Local Unit",
    "Ans3": "Advance Logical Unit",
    "Ans4": "None of these",
    "correct": "Arithmetic Logic Unit"
  },
  {
    "id": "3",
    "Question": "Which is the correct name of a variable?\n(A) -var (B) var-1 (C) _var (D) var_1",
    "Ans1": "Only (A)",
    "Ans2": "Only (B)",
    "Ans3": "Both (A) and (B)",
    "Ans4": "Both (C) and (D)",
    "correct": "Both (C) and (D)"
  },
  {
    "id": "4",
    "Question": "What type of declaration is it? \n unsigned num;",
    "Ans1": "num is an unsigned integer.",
    "Ans2": "num is an unsigned character.",
    "Ans3": "num is an unsigned float",
    "Ans4": "Itâ€™s an invalid declaration.",
    "correct": "num is an unsigned integer."
  },
  {
    "id": "5",
    "Question": "Which statement does not require semicolon?",
    "Ans1": "goto xyz",
    "Ans2": "int x=20",
    "Ans3": "#define MAX 1000",
    "Ans4": "do{ ... }while(count<=100)e",
    "correct": "#define MAX 1000"
  },
  {
    "id": "6",
    "Question": "INSERT, UPDATE and DELETE statements belong to",
    "Ans1": "DQL Language",
    "Ans2": "DDL Language",
    "Ans3": "DCL Language",
    "Ans4": "DML Language",
    "correct": "DML Language"
  },
  {
    "id": "7",
    "Question": "What is Schema?",
    "Ans1": "To identify the record uniquely",
    "Ans2": "To normalize the database",
    "Ans3": "Overall description of the database",
    "Ans4": "To reduce data redundancy",
    "correct": "Overall description of the database"
  },
  {
    "id": "8",
    "Question": " Which module gives control of the CPU to the process selected by the short-term scheduler?",
    "Ans1": "dispatcher",
    "Ans2": "interrupt",
    "Ans3": "scheduler",
    "Ans4": "None of these",
    "correct": "dispatcher"
  },
  {
    "id": "9",
    "Question": "Which one of the following can not be scheduled by the kernel?",
    "Ans1": "kernel level thread",
    "Ans2": "user level thread",
    "Ans3": "none of the mentioned",
    "Ans4": "process",
    "correct": "user level thread"
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "Question": "Process are classified into different groups in",
    "Ans1": "shortest job scheduling algorithm",
    "Ans2": " round robin scheduling algorithm",
    "Ans3": "priority scheduling algorithm",
    "Ans4": "multilevel queue scheduling algorithm",
    "correct": "multilevel queue scheduling algorithm"
  }

]
}
